<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>OpenAlex – Students &amp; Nederlandse instellingen (2025)</title><link>https://openalex.org/</link><description>Publicaties met 'students' uit 2025 gelinkt aan Nederlandse universiteiten</description><item><title>Enhancing the quality and reproducibility of research: Preferred Evaluation of Cognitive and Neuropsychological Studies - The PECANS statement for human studies</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410890886</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410890886</guid><description>(Preferred (i) (ii) (iii) (iv) Abstract And Are Cognitive Delphi Evaluation Neuropsychological PECANS Studies), The These This Through To We a academic across address addressing agencies; all also analysis, and approaching assessing authors broader but checklist cognitive committees community. comprehensive confidence.” consensus-building convened conveying crisis culture data design, designed details drawing editors effectively emerged enhance ensure essential ethics evaluation, evolved execution, experimental experts face fields final form. foster fraction from funding guide has highlighted improve in including: individual inferences inquiry intended international into introduce is iterative its journal journey method. methodology necessary neuropsychology neuropsychology, not numerous of only panel papers phase, planning, practices. pressing process projects proof-of-concept protocols? providing psychology publication. quality questions replicability reporting reports; represent reproducibility research research. research; researchers results? reviewers rigor rigorous rounds sciences scientific seeking serve shortcomings shortcomings, specialized stakeholders students study that the their these through to tool transparency two various versatile voting we writing. “crisis</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Factors involved in vulvar pain during sexual activity and persistence in sexual activity amidst pain</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410850629</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410850629</guid><description>(80.0%) (limited (low) (no) 15.0% 18 277 33 41.0% 42.0% 65.0% = A Dutch Engagement Engaging Evidence Low N Of PVI Participants The These University a activity activity, affected agency, aims all always and as associations at autonomous avoid behaviours), between by common, communicate communicating communication, continue contribute definition despite did distress, do during endure engagement engaging experience experiences experiencing factors female focus function, half in included included. inclusive indicating intercourse intimate least light limited low majority may measures mediated mediators. more most motivation motivation. not of often old. on one or other outcome pain pain, pain. painful participants partly partners. penile-vaginal present primary psychosocial related relationship relevance reported restrictive sample satisfaction satisfaction. self-esteem, sex sex, sexual shed significantly so sometimes sometimes, specific students study such suggests tend than that the their these time time. to variables. vulvar was were when with women women, years</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Equal rights to move? Public attitudes towards the free movement of patients, students and workers in the EU</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410841703</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410841703</guid><description>6000 Against European Germany. Health The To Union, We While a also among an and are as attitudes, backdrop both but case compares conducted cornerstones debates depends development differentiated draws drivers end, evidence find focuses for free higher in incoming increases increasing integration is less levels mobility mobility. movement moving. not of on one original outgoing patient patients people pressing project, public question remains respondents results reveal rights. socio-economic status student students study support supported survey than that the this those to whether who worker workers,</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Students: Using Positioning Theory and Frame Analysis to Explore Power Dynamics in Mentoring Relationships</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410822614</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410822614</guid><description>Discussion: Introduction: It Making Methods: Non-participant Power Results: Students The This We a align also analysis analysis. and as audio axes, be being better build but by can case-study combined continuous crucial diaries. discursive do documented doing draws during dyads dynamics empirical empowerment, enabled enact enactments expectations experiences, experiences. explicit explores findings flux, four frame frames framework. from function gatekeeper general goals have hierarchy, how imposed in inherently insight integration internship. internships. interviews introducing is is, it learning making mentoring mentors; mentors’ multiple not not. novel observations of on operates operationalized opportunities or participate periodic perspective plays positioning potential power power, power. power; practice practice. provide recognizing relational relationship. relationships relationships. resistance, responsibilities resulted role shape situated social solely starts students students: students’ study supporting that the their themselves theoretical theory through tied to took two undergraduate understanding versus vested view was were whether with</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Team-based learning (TBL) in health professions education: A systematic review on its conceptual elements and outcomes</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410810316</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410810316</guid><description>(1.12-12.29%). (171, (4.47%) (HPE), (TBL) (e.g. (element 179 1904 2016 2023. 95.53%) A ERIC Eight Embase, F G), HPE Higher JBI June Kirkpatrick's Learning Medline, Michaelsen's Moreover, Most Much New PRISMA PsychInfo PubMed, Since TBL Team-Based The This To Two World a academic accumulating address already and applied as authors been better between both calls checklists clinical coded communication comprehensive conceptual conduct criteria. current databases deeper demonstrating develop education effect effects elements evaluate evaluating examined examines existing experience extracted for future gaps graduate guide guidelines have health healthcare. important in in-person inclusion increasingly independently investigated investigations is learning leaving level levels literature.[Box: lower met model more necessary. of offline on online online, outcomes outcomes, outcomes. outline overview performance. positive potential practice. professions published quality rarely reasoning) recently, remaining remains report research resulted review. rigorous scarce search searched see selected skills stimulate student studied. studies studies. such systematic text]. that the their this through to underexplored. undergraduate understand used using were which</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Motor and prosocial skills relate to enjoyment and physical activity levels during primary school recess</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410694585</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410694585</guid><description>(LPA) (MVPA) (averaged (mean 50.4% 9.0 = Accelerometers Activity Athletic Children Children's Dutch Enjoyment LPA, MVPA MVPA. Motor Multilevel One Physical Prosocial Scale. Skill Special This Track, Yet, a about activities activity age aimed and are assessed at attention be behaviour behaviour. boys). but capture children children's cross-sectional determined during emphasising engage enjoyable enjoyment enjoyment, enjoyment. equation examine factors fifty-four for foster four guidelines. have herein. hundred importance important in is known levels levels, levels. light little lower measured meeting models moderate-to-vigorous motor negatively not of offers one opportunities outdoor over paid participated partly physical play positively possibilities primary prosocial recess recesses). related relations revealed risk role school should skill skills structural students study teacher-report, that the thousand to used using variety via was were who with years,</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Teachers’ needs in mainstream secondary schools regarding the inclusion of students with Autism Spectrum Disorder: a cross-country study</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410699012</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410699012</guid><description /><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Challenging cases of hyponatremia incorrectly interpreted by ChatGPT</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410596951</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410596951</guid><description>(ChatGPT-3.5) 1 2 2%, 2023 2023, 2024 2024, 2024. 3 3.5 4 4. 46 57%, 65%, 76%, 81% Addison's Because Canada, Case Chat ChatGPT ChatGPT, ChatGPT-3.5 ChatGPT. Concurrent December Generative In Neither Netherlands, No Our Patients, Pre-trained Responses September South-Africa, Taiwan, The There These To Transformer USA, We a adequate advice after all also analyzing and any are artificial as assessment aware be but by case case. cases cases, cases. cause challenging clinical clinicians clinicians, clinicians. compared complex concerning consequences contributing correctly crucial current currently described diagnosed diagnosis diagnosis. diagnostic difficult disease does education educators efficient errors, evaluate evaluated evaluating features. for four free frequently given have health hyponatremia hyponatremia. iatrogenic improvement in inadequate increasingly intelligence interesting is known limitations. literature major management may medical medicine, mismanagement, missed months morbidity. most no nor not observed of often one original overcome pathophysiology, patients physicians possibility, possibly presented previously previously, previously. problems, professionals, proper properly publication, published recognized recommend recommendations recommended request required respectively same shortcomings should single small source students study substantial suggested suggestions suggestions. support techniques ten that the their therapeutic therapy therapy. this those times to tool. treatment two use used using version version. was well were whereas whose with</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Assess Global Education Quality: The Global Education Quality Index and Its Cross-National Comparisons</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410611198</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410611198</guid><description>(GEQI) 2009 2018, 62 Assurance Basic Comparison Design/Approach/Methods Development Education European Findings First, Furthermore, GEQI GEQI. Global Index Input-Process-Outcome” Operation Originality/Value Our Overall, Postsecondary Purpose Quality School Second, The These Third, This Union We a academic accessibility across actionable advanced allocation an analysis and assesses assessment. at attainment attributed based basic be compare components. conducted consistently construct contexts, countries countries/regions countries/regions. cultural data descriptive development differences dimensions. distinct dominate education educational encompasses evaluate evaluates exhibit for framework from global government improvement. improvements. in indicates infrastructure. insights into introduces investment is landscape level. maps may measures multiple of offers on or other patterns performance. policy pools positions practices, professional provides quality quantitative reforms. regional regions representative resource robust scores. snapshot social specific strengths students' study sub-indices, systemic that the three to tool top utilizing variations weaknesses while worldwide. “Educational</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Flow and longform reading. Notes from an exploratory case study</title><link>https://openalex.org/W4410613068</link><guid>https://openalex.org/W4410613068</guid><description>Abstract Drawing Finally, Further Observations Our The This Towards We When a academic addressing also an and are as aspects attention. available. battle between bodily but by case changed. cognition, conditions consistently continue contrast contributes decline deep, desk. device devices devices, differ differ, digital digitally, distributed during effort, embodied emerge emerging enactment end engagement especially established even examine exploratory extended extent findings flow fluctuate focused for from future greater highlights how idle immersed importance in in-phase’, increases increasingly influencing instead interruptions. interruptions: investigates is later left literature longform modes: more more. natural need not observed of often on once one only other our paper participants’ particular perspectives phase positions possible possibly presence present print, printed problem. process processes. reader readers readers’ reading reading, recognized remain requires research restlessness results revealed role screens. seem self-initiated session session, sessions, settings. settings: settling settling-in shifts showed significant social students studies study such suggest suggesting systematic systematically task task” text, texts that that, the theories these they this through throughout time to tools training trajectories two uneasy unfolds. university various when with would ‘settling “on</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>